<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>open hardware on Foosn PTE Ltd</title><link>https://foosn.com/tags/open-hardware/</link><description>Recent content in open hardware on Foosn PTE Ltd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foosn.com/tags/open-hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Farpatch: Wireless, Remote Debugging</title><link>https://foosn.com/products/farpatch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://foosn.com/products/farpatch/</guid><description>Farpatch is a wireless debugger, capable of programming, debugging, and interacting with a wide range of microcontrollers. Powered by the BlackMagic debug software, Farpatch supports inspecting memory, single-stepping code, and adding breakpoints to your project. You don’t need to install any drivers, just join Farpatch to your wireless network, or let it run in AP mode if you’re not near an access point.
Farpatch can also draw power from your board, supports board voltages of 1.</description></item><item><title>Fomu: An FPGA in your USB Port</title><link>https://foosn.com/products/fomu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://foosn.com/products/fomu/</guid><description>Fomu is the easiest way to get started with FPGA or RISC-V development Fomu is a programmable FPGA device that fits inside a USB port. It has four buttons, an RGB LED, and an FPGA that is compatible with a fully open source chain and capable of running a RISC-V core. Fomu comes in a custom plastic enclosure that slots perfectly into a USB Type-A port.
Python, RISC-V, FPGA, All Open Fomu has Python With 128 kilobytes of RAM and a large amount of storage, Fomu is powerful enough to run Python natively.</description></item><item><title>Tomu: A Computer in your USB Port</title><link>https://foosn.com/products/tomu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://foosn.com/products/tomu/</guid><description>Tomu is a programmable computer that fits inside a USB port. It is user-programmable, has two buttons and two LEDs, and can be used for everything from a hobbyist device to a U2F security token. Simple, Open, Flexible, Easy
Tomu is simple. It hides out in a USB port of your computer and waits for you to use it. It has two LEDs to let you know what’s going on, and two buttons for interaction.</description></item></channel></rss>